forabeautifulweb.com 2011-10-05

# Privacy policy | For A Beautiful Web

This privacy policy details how we handle and protect your contact and personal information. It applies to any information you provide to us when using our web site, contacting us by email, phone or when you use our online ticketing system.

### What information do we collect?

When you register for one of our events or register your interest in hearing about future events, we collect information that is necessary for us to do what you have asked us to do. This information may include:

  * Your name and the name of your company or organisation
  * Your email address, address and phone number(s)
  * Any special requirements you may have
  * Your credit/debit card number, expiry date and billing address

### How is this information used?

We may use this information to:

  * Process your order and create your tax invoice and ticket(s)
  * Send you ongoing information regarding our events
  * Let you know about related upcoming events

### Disclosing your information to third parties

When we collect your contact and personal information, we will never share it outside of Stuff and Nonsense Ltd. unless you have authorised us to do so. Will not we sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your contact and personal information. We may photograph or video our events including our speakers and attendees for use online or in print. By attending, you give us the right to take such photographs and videos and to use your likeness in our promotional materials.

### Contact information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us by email at [2010@forabeautifulweb.com](mailto:2010@forabeautifulweb.com), telephone us on +44 (0)1745 851848, or write to: For A Beautiful Web. [Stuff and Nonsense Ltd.](http://www.stuffandnonsense.co.uk/), The Cow Shed Studio, Eversleigh, Gwaenysgor, Flintshire, North Wales, LL18 6EJ, UK.

### Looking for fantastic   
web site design?

[Stuff and Nonsense](http://stuffandnonsense.co.uk/) is a small, but popular, web design studio, founded and led by designer and author Andy Clarke. [Use this form](http://stuffandnonsense.co.uk/company/contact) you are looking for fantastic web site design or call us on (01745) 851–848

If you need to send us something, our postal address is:

The Cow Shed Studio, Eversleigh

Gwaenysgor

Flintshire, North Wales

LL18 6EJ

Registered in England & Wales   
Company No. 03687563   
VAT No. 728 7958 71.
